[
    {
        "question": "Masculin",
        "answers": [
            "der",
            "das",
            "die",
            "Nothing"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Neutral",
        "answers": [
            "die",
            "der",
            "das",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Feminin",
        "answers": [
            "der",
            "das",
            "N/A",
            "die"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Plural",
        "answers": [
            "das",
            "die",
            "der",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "maskulin",
        "answers": [
            "ein",
            "eine",
            "-",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "femenin",
        "answers": [
            "-",
            "eine",
            "ein",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Plural",
        "answers": [
            "N/A",
            "eine",
            "ein",
            "-"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "maskulin",
        "answers": [
            "kein",
            "keine",
            "N/A",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "femenin",
        "answers": [
            "kein",
            "keine",
            "N/A",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "plural",
        "answers": [
            "N/A",
            "kein",
            "keine",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "maskulin",
        "answers": [
            "mein",
            "meine",
            "N/A",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "femenin",
        "answers": [
            "N/A",
            "mein",
            "N/A",
            "meine"
        ],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "plural",
        "answers": [
            "meine",
            "N/A",
            "mein",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Akkusativ masculin",
        "answers": [
            "den",
            "das",
            "die",
            "N/A"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answers": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answers": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answers": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answers": [
            "",
            "",
            "",
            ""
        ],
        "correct": 0
    }
]